a-dec.com 2012-10-14

# A-dec Inc. - Dental Equipment Solutions

A‑dec takes your privacy very seriously and this privacy policy documents our commitment to protecting the privacy of all our website users and customers. By visiting a‑dec.com and providing any personal information to A‑dec, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy.

**1\. Collecting Information**  
A‑dec receives and stores any information that you enter on our website, send to us in an order form, or give to us in any other way. [We keep this information only so long as is necessary to provide the services that we describe below.] There are two basic types of information that we may collect. First, we collect anonymous, aggregate information from all visitors to our website. This type of information is never linked to any personally identifiable information and is only used to generate statistical reports about the use of our website. 

Second, when you request information about A‑dec products or services, we collect personally identifiable information including your telephone number.

**2\. Our Use of Your Personal Information**  
Our primary goal in collecting information from you is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience while using our services. This allows us to make you aware of and offer you products, services and features that we feel will help meet your needs. Additionally, only with this information can we fulfill your requests for products, services, literature, and support. If you choose, you can easily be removed from our promotional mailing list, which is used exclusively by A‑dec. Simply reply to any message with a request to be removed, or call Customer Service at 1.800.547.1883 and give one of our representatives the email address you wish to have removed. 

**3\. Sharing Personal Information with Third Parties**  
We may provide to our third-party vendors the anonymous, aggregate information we collect from all visitors to our website. As we mentioned above, these statistics will include no personal information. 

In the course of operating our business, we might share your personally identifiable information with third parties. Any disclosure of such information will be done only in accordance with this policy. 

**_Affiliates:_** We may provide personal information to our affiliated companies. These are companies that own us or are a parent company of a company which owns us or are a company which we own or which is owned by the same company we are owned by. Our affiliates are required to adhere to this Privacy Policy in the same manner as we are. 

_**Companies that work for or with A‑dec:**_ We may share your personal information with unaffiliated companies that work for or with us for the sole purpose of providing you with valuable services and products you've requested or already enjoy. These companies may need to use your personal information to assist us in fulfilling your requests or processing your transactions. These companies are not permitted to use your personal information for any other purpose. 

In addition, we may share your personal information with unaffiliated companies to market, advertise, and promote products and services to you. This includes persons and entities with whom we have entered into a joint marketing agreement, where we together market either our products and services or those of our marketing partner. We enter into contractual agreements with these companies prohibiting them from disclosing or using our customer information other than to carry out the purposes for which the information was disclosed. These companies are in no way authorized to sell, rent or trade your personal information. 

_**Protection of A‑dec and others:**_ We may disclose your information, including personally identifiable information, in special cases when we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with the legal process such as, but not limited to situations when we are required to do so by federal, state or local laws and regulations or when we receive a subpoena or are ordered by a court to do so; (b) protect and defend our rights; or (c) act to protect the rights, property, and other interests of our users or others. 

_**Business transfers:**_ As we continue to develop our business, we might buy or sell subsidiaries or business units. In these transactions, customer information generally is one of the assets transferred but it remains subject to the restrictions set forth in any pre-existing privacy policy. Also, in the event that A‑dec is acquired by a third party, customer information would likely be one of the acquired assets. 

_**Other parties:**_ While our contracts with third parties limit their use of personal information, we cannot and do not guarantee that every third party will comply with these obligations. It is possible that such a third party could breach its obligation and use your personal information in a way contrary to our policy. Also, this website contains links to other sites and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that you visit. 

**4\. Security**  
A‑dec strives to protect the information provided by our users and customers. All of our collected information is stored behind a secured firewall which restricts access from third parties. Additionally, the servers that store your personally identifiable information are housed in a secure environment. We also make an effort to protect your information off-line. Only personnel who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. All employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Despite these precautions, given the nature of the Internet and the fact that network security measures are not infallible, we cannot guarantee the security of your information. This is especially true for information you transmit to us via email. We have no way of protecting that information until it reaches us. 

When registering for access to a secure area of the site, we will ask you to select a username and password. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. We will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Also, remember to sign out of the registered site and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence when accessing your computer.

**5\. Correcting, Updating, Deleting and Deactivating Personal Information**  
You have the right to access your personal information collected by us. If your personally identifiable information changes, you may correct, update or delete our record of your personally identifiable information. Simply send email to [customerservice@a‑dec.com] or call Customer Service at 1.800.547.1883.

**6\. Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
We may, from time to time, update this Privacy Policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat your personal information by sending a notice to your designated email address or by placing a prominent notice on our website. You will also be given the choice as to whether or not we may use your information in this different manner. 

**7\. Contact Information**  
If you have any questions about our privacy policy or if you feel that your information has been used or disclosed in violation of this policy, please contact us at:

Phone: 503.538.9471  
Email: webmaster@a‑dec.com
